# **CHRIS HUNTER**

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



## CONTACT

- +447493934871
- chriswhunter89@gmail.com
- https://github.com/chriswhunter89
- in www.linkedin.com/in/chris-hunter89

### PROFILE

Irish. 32 Years old. Based in London.

Having worked as a mechanical engineer for the past 8 years, I have embarked on a new journey as a full-stack developer. After over 1 year of coding including graduating from Le Wagon's Full-Stack Web Development bootcamp, I am ready to utilise my newfound skills to help your company succeed.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Le Wagon London - Batch #697

Le Wagon Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp July 2021 - September 2021

# BEng (Hons) Energy & Building Services Engineering

University of Ulster, Jordanstown Sept. 2010 - June 2014

# SKILLS

**PYTHON** 

RUBY

RUBY ON RAILS

0.0.P

DATABASES & ACTIVE RECORD

HTML / CSS / JS

HTTP & AJAX

GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

TRAVELLIST | WWW.TRAVELLIST.UK

A website for avid travellers to track destinations, plan their trips and store their memories for their destinations with dedicated photo albums. Please view at <a href="https://www.travellist.uk">www.travellist.uk</a>

#### WORKWISE | WWW.WORKWISE.LIVE

A collaborative online platform that assists companies to search for and purchase properties to suit their business needs. View our demo @ https://youtu.be/6KB72NU5j6A

# **EXPERIENCE**

CONSULTANT - CHOICE OPTIONS LTD FEB 2022 - PRESENT

- Working as a consultant for start-up building a multivertical recommender app.
- Creating figma prototypes for user testing.

# MECHANICAL ENGINEER & ENERGY ASSESSOR 2013 - 2020

- Lead engineer for numerous projects from concept to completion.
- Detailed design & thermal analysis of proposals.
- Regular client liaison and leading meetings.

### PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Sports I have played rugby and gaelic football for most of my life and also enjoy watching professional sport.
- Music I listen to a wide range of music and I also play the drums.
- Charities I enjoy volunteering and fund-raising.